Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Send the antidote over quickly.
أرسلوا الترياق بسرعة.
Help me.
ساعدني.
How do you want me to help?
كيف تريدني أن أساعدك؟
Do you know who I am?
هل تعرف من أنا؟
Lin Moqing.
لين موكينج.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
How did I get here?
كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
You didn't lose your memory again, did you?
لم تفقد ذاكرتك مرة أخرى، أليس كذلك؟
Last night, you begged me
الليلة الماضية، توسلت إلي
to help you.
لمساعدتك.
You're not trying to avoid responsibility, are you?
أنت لا تحاول التهرب من المسؤولية، أليس كذلك؟
What exactly happened?
ما الذي حدث بالضبط؟
The symptoms will disappear in ten minutes.
ستختفي الأعراض في غضون عشر دقائق.
I'll be going now, Mr. Lin.
سأذهب الآن يا سيد لين.
Are you angry because
هل أنت غاضب لأن
I didn't do anything
لم أفعل شيئاً
last night?
ليلة أمس؟
Then why are you still here?
إذاً لماذا ما زلت هنا؟
Is this how you treat your
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تعامل بها...
life-saving hero?
بطل إنقاذ الأرواح؟
Why weren't you this fierce when you
لماذا لم تكن بهذه الشراسة عندما...
were getting drunk last night?
هل كنا ثملين الليلة الماضية؟
I thought there might be something wrong with the wine,
ظننت أن هناك ربما مشكلة ما في النبيذ،
I even had the waiter replace the wine.
حتى أنني طلبت من النادل استبدال النبيذ.
But I didn't expect
لكنني لم أتوقع
Duan Chenglin to put the drug in the cup.
دوان تشنغلين يضع الدواء في الكأس.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
don't put yourself
لا تعرض نفسك للخطر
in danger again.
في خطر مرة أخرى.
Because it hurts me.
لأنه يؤلمني.
[Affair between brother-in-law and sister-in-law]
[علاقة بين صهر وزوجة أخ]
[This morning,]
[هذا الصباح،]
[Lin Group was exposed to an ethics storm.]
[تعرضت مجموعة لين لعاصفة أخلاقية.]
[Lanhe Group's CEO, Lan Hewei,]
[الرئيس التنفيذي لمجموعة Lanhe، Lan Hewei]
[and the second son of Lin Group,]
[وابن لين الثاني]
[of Lin Group, Lin Moqing,]
[من مجموعة لين، لين موكينغ،]
[caused a crisis in the family.]
[تسبب في أزمة في الأسرة.]
[Now,]
[الآن،]
[the president of Lin Group, Lin Mojiao,]
[رئيس مجموعة لين، لين موجياو]
[has not responded to this matter yet.]
[لم يرد على هذا الأمر بعد.]
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
the stock of the Group has fallen sharply today.
انخفض سهم المجموعة بشكل حاد اليوم.
That's not enough.
هذا لا يكفي.
As planned,
كما هو مخطط له،
let the rumor continue to ferment.
دع الشائعات تستمر في الانتشار.
Yes.
نعم.
Five companies have already
خمس شركات قد فعلت ذلك بالفعل
have paused their cooperation with us.
لقد أوقفوا تعاونهم معنا.
Yeah. Well...
أجل. حسناً...
What do we do now?
ماذا نفعل الآن؟
What a mess!
يا لها من فوضى!
As the head of the group,
بصفته رئيس المجموعة،
you must explain this to the board.
يجب عليك شرح هذا للمجلس.
Everyone,
الجميع،
this issue started because of me.
بدأت هذه المشكلة بسببي.
I'll handle it with all my effort,
سأتعامل مع الأمر بكل ما أوتيت من جهد.
and I won't avoid my responsibilities.
ولن أتهرب من مسؤولياتي.
Currently, all stocks of Lanhe Group
حالياً، جميع أسهم مجموعة لانهي
have been continuously falling,
كانت تتراجع باستمرار،
and all projects have been suspended.
وتم تعليق جميع المشاريع.
The fastest way to resolve this
أسرع طريقة لحل هذه المشكلة
is for you to temporarily step down
هذا يعني أن تتنحى مؤقتًا
as the CEO of Blue Crane.
بصفته الرئيس التنفيذي لشركة بلو كرين.
Li Hao,
لي هاو,
Ms. Lan just took over the company.
تولت السيدة لان إدارة الشركة للتو.
We should give her a chance.
ينبغي أن نمنحها فرصة.
We can give her a chance,
يمكننا أن نمنحها فرصة،
but time is not on our side.
لكن الوقت ليس في صالحنا.
If we keep dragging this out,
إذا استمررنا في إطالة أمد هذا الأمر،
who will be responsible
من سيكون المسؤول؟
will be responsible
سيكون مسؤولاً
for the losses? Yeah.
بالنسبة للخسائر؟ نعم.
Exactly. Who's responsible?
بالضبط. من المسؤول؟
Give me three days.
أعطني ثلاثة أيام.
If I can't turn things around,
إذا لم أستطع تغيير الأمور،
I'll resign as the CEO
سأستقيل من منصب الرئيس التنفيذي
of Blue Crane.
من بلو كرين.
Hitting the sandbag is so boring.
ضرب كيس الرمل أمر ممل للغاية.
Are you just going to be easily defeated like this?
هل ستُهزم بسهولة هكذا؟
Is this how determined you are to get revenge?
هل أنت مصمم على الانتقام إلى هذه الدرجة؟
I won't give up.
أنا لن أستسلم.
As long as you still have this land,
طالما أنك ما زلت تملك هذه الأرض،
there's still a chance.
لا تزال هناك فرصة.
Don't lose your composure.
لا تفقد رباطة جأشك.
And, next time,
وفي المرة القادمة،
I won't go easy on you.
لن أتساهل معك.
In three days,
في غضون ثلاثة أيام،
if I can't resolve this crisis,
إذا لم أستطع حل هذه الأزمة،
I'll have to leave Blue Crane.
سأضطر إلى مغادرة بلو كرين.
Give me two people.
أعطني شخصين.
Hello? Brother,
أهلا؟ أخي،
I'll be there soon.
سأكون هناك قريباً.
Slow down. You know what?
تمهل. أتعرف ماذا؟
Brother loves fruits the most.
أخي يحب الفواكه أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
You can eat when you get back.
يمكنك تناول الطعام عند عودتك.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Lan, Lan, Lan... Mr. Lan,
اللعنة، اللعنة، اللعنة... يا سيد اللعنة،
don't you love drinking?
ألا تحب الشرب؟
I'll treat you
سأعاملك بالمثل
to a
إلى ​
big drink.
مشروب كبير.
You can't hold your liquor?
ألا تستطيع التحكم في نفسك عند شرب الكحول؟
Mr. Lan,
السيد لان،
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I was just following orders.
كنتُ أنفذ الأوامر فحسب.
I...
أنا...
If I tell you who it is,
إذا أخبرتك من هو،
do you think I don't know already?
أتظن أنني لا أعرف ذلك بالفعل؟
Today, I'll make sure Mr. Duan
اليوم، سأتأكد من أن السيد دوان
have a good time.
وقتا ممتعا.
I didn't expect
لم أتوقع
that you are so impressive
أنك مثير للإعجاب للغاية
when you get angry.
عندما تغضب.
But,
لكن،
don't forget
لا تنسى
why you came back this time.
لماذا عدت هذه المرة؟